أعوذ بِٱللَّهِ مِنَ ٱلشَّيْطَـٰنِ ٱلرَّجِيمِ
بِسْمِ اللهِ الرَّحْمٰنِ الرَّحِيْمِ
(36:2) يسٓ (36:1) وَٱلْقُرْءَانِ ٱلْحَكِيمِ
(36:4) إِنَّكَ لَمِنَ ٱلْمُرْسَلِينَ (36:3) عَلَىٰ صِرَٰطٍ مُّسْتَقِيمٍ
(36:5) تَنزِيلَ ٱلْعَزِيزِ ٱلرَّحِيمِ
(36:6) لِتُنذِرَ قَوْمًا مَّآ أُنذِرَ ءَابَآؤُهُمْ فَهُمْ غَـٰفِلُونَ
(36:7) لَقَدْ حَقَّ ٱلْقَوْلُ عَلَىٰٓ أَكْثَرِهِمْ فَهُمْ لَا يُؤْمِنُونَ
(36:8) إِنَّا جَعَلْنَا فِىٓ أَعْنَـٰقِهِمْ أَغْلَـٰلًا فَهِىَ إِلَى ٱلْأَذْقَانِ فَهُم مُّقْمَحُونَ
وَجَعَلْنَا مِنۢ بَيْنِ أَيْدِيهِمْ سَدًّا وَمِنْ خَلْفِهِمْ سَدًّا فَأَغْشَيْنَـٰهُمْ فَهُمْ لَا يُبْصِرُونَ (36:9)
(36:10) وَسَوَآءٌ عَلَيْهِمْ ءَأَنذَرْتَهُمْ أَمْ لَمْ تُنذِرْهُمْ لَا يُؤْمِنُونَ
إِنَّمَا تُنذِرُ مَنِ ٱتَّبَعَ ٱلذِّكْرَ وَخَشِىَ ٱلرَّحْمَـٰنَ بِٱلْغَيْبِ ۖ فَبَشِّرْهُ بِمَغْفِرَةٍ وَأَجْرٍ كَرِيمٍ (36:11)
إِنَّا نَحْنُ نُحْىِ ٱلْمَوْتَىٰ وَنَكْتُبُ مَا قَدَّمُوا۟ وَءَاثَـٰرَهُمْ ۚ وَكُلَّ شَىْءٍ (36:12) أَحْصَيْنَـٰهُ فِىٓ إِمَامٍۢ مُّبِينٍۢ
We praise God, and we bear witness that there is no god except the one God.
And we declare that all devotion and all worship is directed to God alone.
SURA 39 أَلَا لِلَّهِ ٱلدِّينُ ٱلْخَالِصُ devotion and worship belong to God alone.
Some of you probably saw this bombshell where there is announcement
that I have been commissioned a messenger of God.
And this is probably the most difficult announcement that I have ever come up with.
But something that I have known since 1980. And you can see that I was, I was coward.
I was afraid to come up with it. I dreaded the time when I may have to announce it.
Because there is a general tendency to resent anybody saying - I am going to use a wrong statement now,
but this is what the resentment is for. Generally, people resent somebody saying I'm better than you
or what appears to be saying I am better than you.
And even the Quran condemns such a statement, in SURA 4, God says note those who exalt themselves.
God is the one who exalts whomever He wills without the least injustice.
The resentment in this case results from two things: ignorance and idol-worship.
Ignorance, because the Quran teaches us that a messenger of God
is not necessarily better than anyone else in the congregation.
In SURA 18, from verses 60 to verse 82, we see that God picked out one of the biggest messengers,
Moses, one that God said I made you for myself. (20:41) وَٱصْطَنَعْتُكَ لِنَفْسِى I made you for Me.
And in other place, God said (20:39) لِتُصْنَعَ عَلَىٰ عَيْنِىٓ I had you made before My eyes.
And we see in those verses that God sent Moses to one of our servants, whom we bestowed,
we gave mercy and knowledge.
And Moses proved to be a lousy student.
So, this teaches us that a messenger of God is not necessarily better than
anyone else in the congregation.
I can think of quite a few of you whom I consider better than me.
I see people, when I was their age, I used to go to the Saints and ask for help.
I was an idol worshiper, when I was that age.
Yet here they are, a lot younger. They have 20-year head start, compared to me. And so
This is the first thing. Ignorance causes this resentment.
Idol worship because the people idolize the messenger of God and they made him next to God.
They made him a god besides God. So, when you mention the word messenger of God,
they are awed, you know.
But the truth is, a messenger of God is - the Quran repeats a human being like you.
or in colloquial, local terms a flopster like the rest of us whom we can kid around and who can be silly.
What is more the Quran teaches that a messenger of God... if a person is picked out as a messenger of God, a commissioned messenger of God....there are kinds of messengers
does not even guarantee Heaven.
And we see this in SURAH 39 verse 65
where it says it has been revealed to you and to those before you that if you ever fall in idolatry,
all you work will be nullified and you will be among the losers.
So, a messenger of God does not even guarantee heaven.
And this is why we see in SURA 21, verse 28 that the messengers are worried about their own neck.
We are all familiar with these verses. But the people who have either ignorance or idolatry in them,
they resent an announcement like this.
If a person is picked as a messenger of God, it's a difficult job. It's a very difficult job.
There is no material gain out of it. I certainly will not allow a single penny to enter my personal pocket because of this or because of religious reasons.
I'm not a professional religionist and I will not allow a penny to enter my pocket from religious activities
Because then the motive changes.
And the Quran repeats stay with those who do not ask you for wages.
The Quran says in SURA 49... Quran gives us the criteria of who is better than whom.
And in says in Arabic
(49:13) إِنَّ أَكْرَمَكُمْ عِندَ ٱللَّهِ أَتْقَىٰكُمْ
The best among you is the most righteous.
It didn't say the best among you is the messenger of God, or the richest, or the tallest,
or the most knowledgeable.
The best among you is the most righteous.
So, all these things will teach us that messenger of God is no big deal.
It is just a vehicle that God uses to communicate with us.
A center of information.
And with it goes a difficult job, a very difficult job, the abuse, the slandering, the threats.
And God says....I believe it's in 42:51. Yes. In SURA 42, verse 51, God says that
No human being can communicate with God, except through three ways:
inspiration, or from behind a barrier, or through a messenger
that through whom God spreads certain information.
So, people will know this is reliable information, that this is from God.
We are people who follow the Quran, the whole Quran and nothing but the Quran.
Therefore, anybody, and this means anybody, who brings any information must conform to the Quran.
The whole Quran, nothing but the Quran.
And if anyone, and underline anyone,
comes up with any information that is not confirmed by the Quran, we tell him forget it!
We don't accept it.
So, the criterion is preaching, confirming existing scripture, the Quran and nothing else.
No innovations.
Now, we come to the question: is it possible that we receive a messenger from God?
If you ask an average Muhammadan, they will tell you Muhammad was the last messenger.
But they have no basis, for saying this. And the Quran gives us a precedent since Joseph, the prophet Joseph.
When he died, the Quran teaches us that the people said okay, that was the last messenger,
we'll never see another messenger after that.
So, this is a human tendency.
And the Muhammdans claim that Muhammad was the last messenger. He's not.
In SURA 33, verse 40, God says Muhammad was not the father of any of your men. He was a messenger
of God and the final prophet.
So, here we see a distinction between prophet and messenger.
A prophet is one who delivers a scripture, like Jesus, Moses, Muhammad. They are prophets.
And we this clearly in SURA 3, verse 81, where God says that He made a covenant with the prophets
that He will give them the scripture and wisdom.
So, here we have the definition of a prophet.
Then, God made a covenant with us, with you and me, with every human being. He said then,
when a messenger comes to you, confirming existing scripture.
So, there's the definition of a messenger. When a messenger comes to you confirming
existing scripture, you shall believe in him and support him.
God said do you make a pledge with me?
And we all said yes, we do.
And God said you have thus borne witness and I bear witness along with you.
Therefore, it is possible that there will be messengers after Muhammad.
In SURA 7, verse 35, it says o children of Adam, when messengers come to you, reciting
My revelations to you, those of you who believe are the successful ones. This is SURA 7, verse 35.
Obviously, it is for people after the Quran. As a matter of fact, the verse begins by saying o children of Adam.
So, as long as there are children of Adam on this Earth, this verse is valid.
If messengers are coming after Muhammad, what do they look like?
What will a messenger look like after Muhammad?
Just think of any human being. What are his characteristics? You think he'll be walking on water
or walking on the air or coming with 3 angels on each side or something.
He's just one of us, just a human being.
Some people came. I wanna answer the question why, why send a messenger?
Why does God send a messenger?
Why not just go the same way that people have been going? Reading the Quran, following the Quran.
Well, one important element is the test. Because of this covenant that we made with God.
What are you going to do if a messenger of God comes and says worship God alone,
and forget about the human beings; Muhammad, Jesus, Moses or anybody.
You must devote yourself totally to God alone.
One who will preach the Quran, God's proven scripture.
What are you going to do? Are you gonna scoff at him? Are you gonna help him, morally?
Are you gonna rally around him?
What are you going to do? A test.
Another test is the test of ego.
The Quran repeats they said Oh, he just wants to be better than we are. He wants to be a leader.
And this is emphasized throughout the Quran.
You're gonna find some verses in here. And there is in SURA 17, verse 94, it says what
prevented many people from believing was that they said you mean God sent a human being
to be a messenger?
And in SURA 64, verses 5 & 6, I'm gonna read them for you.
Did you not receive the news of those who disbelieved in the past?
They suffered the consequences of their decision and deserved painful retribution. Why?
This is because their messengers went to them with clear revelations, but they said human beings
to guide us?
Thus, they disbelieved and turned away. God does not need them.
So, it's a tremendous test to accept somebody who says he is a messenger of God.
There's an ego here. We're required to kill the ego.
And this applies to all of us. One of the requirements in the Quran.
The egotistic person will resent anything like this and will be deprived.
And God says in the Quran I will divert from my revelations those who are arrogant.
(7:146) سَأَصْرِفُ عَنْ ءَايَـٰتِىَ ٱلَّذِينَ يَتَكَبَّرُونَ فِى ٱلْأَرْض
I will send them away. God will actively send them away.
So, this is something we have to kill, the ego.
So, many people came and said they were messengers of God. Baháʼu'lláh was one of them. And Ghulam Ahmad of Pakistan said he was a messenger of God.
And Joseph Smith, the Mormon leader, said he was a messenger of God.
But God made it mandatory that a messenger comes with proof, certain signs.
Moses brought all kinds of proofs. Saleh brought proofs.
Jesus came with signs that he is authorized and sent by God.
And on that difficult day, a few days ago, when... I'm going to give you all details.
I'm not gonna be mysterious and say I was told this and that and leave it hanging.
I'm going to give you... everything's is gonna be wide open in front of you and I will tell you exactly what happened
in time if the time doesn't help us now.
But this reminds me of the fellow... you've heard this... I told some of you at least this before... but this fellow was the most curious person in town
and he would just ask questions. He'd always ask questions. And one time, he was sitting in the bar or the pub or whatever the place is
and then comes in this man with one leg and he sits next to him and this very curious person... of course, he's curious, you know... how did you lose your leg?
He wants to know.
And the man with one leg knows that he is the most curious person in town.
He would just die to know, how did this fellow lose his leg?
So, he told... the man with the one leg told him, the curious fellow.... told the curious fellow. I will tell you on one condition.
And he said anything... anything... just tell me... anything.... just tell me what to do and I will do it. Just tell me... anything.
He said you ask only one question and you don't ask any questions after that.
He said OK. OK. I do it. Just tell me. How did you lose your leg?
He said it was bitten.
So, I'm sure that curious guy died on the spot because he couldn't ask any more questions.
So I'm not going to be mysterious with you, I'm gonna tell you everything gradually.
But on that difficult day, when I realized that I must announce. I mean, I chickened out for 8 years, now.
I needed some signs and I was shown. I had some signs but I was shown a couple of additional signs on that day.
Now, I will share with you some of the signs that will assure all of us.
Now, the first sign, of course, is the mathematical miracle of the Quran which is very simple and people should have seen it in the last 1400 years.
Literally, thousands of scholars looked in the Quran and counted all its words, its letters, its vowels - those signs, little signs. They counted everything in the Quran.
But they never came up with the mathematical composition of the Quran.
BISMI ALLAH, 19 letters. The number of SURAs 19 times 6. The first revelation, 19 words. The last revelation, 19 words.
All these are simple things that they should have discovered.
But God reserved this for a person called Rashad, as we see
in the index of the Quran page 320
which was printed one year before I was born,
that index. It's a comprehensive index. And on page 320, you'll see that the root word RASHADA is mentioned 19 times.
And this is something that came to us from Turkey. I didn't discover it. It was discovered and sent to us,
as most of you know.
Now, the additional things... Now, I want to give you a piece of new information that shows you the awesome miracle of the Quran that was reserved until this time.
The word God, ALLAH, in the Quran is mentioned 2698 time. When you take every verse in the Quran, where you see the word ALLAH.... every verse... from verse 1 of SURA 1
and you add the numbers of verses, the total is 118123. These are the numbers of verses wherever you see the word God in here. It's awesome.
Because not a single verse was transplanted from its place. Not a single verse was changed.
And not a single word, ALLAH, was dropped out or added in the Quran. So, this is an awesome miracle that did not... was reserved for... God knew in advance
who is going to be fortunate enough or blessed with releasing this information.
Now, if you add all the verses in the SURAHs of the 19 RASHADA and the last name... the last name is also involved there. This is very embarrassing to me but I have to tell you this and share it with you.
But Khalifa is mentioned in the Quran twice.
When you add all the SURAs and verses, the total is 1369 which is 19 times 77.
You add all the SURAs and verses where RASHADA and Khalifa are mentioned. Well, I was not content with that. I'm greedy.
I wanted specific Rashad Khalifa. Specific, Rashad Khalifa. And sure enough, you look up the.... Rashad is mentioned twice... Rashad. This is the way my name is written down.
It is mentioned in Quran twice in SURA 40 verse 29 and verse 38. The Khalifa... they are twice in the Quran. One of them is a bad one and the other's a good one.
The bad Khalifa is Satan which is in SURA 2. And the human Khalifa which is specifically mentioned in Quran in reference to David, the prophet,
one of our favourite prophets, the Psalms.
And this Khalifa is mentioned in SURA 38 verse 26. So, if you add the SURAs and verses connect it with Rashad and the human Khalifa
the total is 171. 19 times 9. So, in other words, you look at every angle and you can see that the signs are connected with the mathematical code.
Now, I will explain to you in detail at another time when we have time, but this is the religion
of IBRAHIM, as we see in the last verse of SURA 22.
(22:78) مِّلَّةَ أَبِيكُمْ إِبْرَٰهِيمَ
This is the religion of your father Abraham. He is the one who named you Muslims before.
Muhammad brought the Quran. And yours truly was blessed with bringing the proof.
I was blessed with the proof of the Quran, and the secrets of the Quran.
When you add Ibrahim, Muhammad and Rashad... The gematrical values of the 3 names.... This is all detailed here...
The total is 855 which is 19x45. And 45 happens to be my age in 1980 when I was told for the first time...
And again I will.... I promise you I'll explain to you how,
But 45, in 1980, which is also 1400, exactly 14 centuries after Muhammad, who was told in the Quran
that he will have 7 pairs, 14 centuries,
among other meanings of the 7 pairs.
So, it is very tight evidence and it suits the age of... computer age.
Now, the secrets of the Quran....the Quran... I mentioned this because it explains to you the revolutionary ideas that I used to come up with once in a while
or the crazy ideas, if you wanna call them that,
like the end of the world. It is very clear in the Quran, but it was not shown before. It's a secret in the Quran.
God knew when the end of the world will be and He put it in His final message.
And we are the generation that was destined to know, to get this secret out of the Quran.
And like the idea that drove a lot of people crazy, that anybody who dies before the age of 40
goes to heaven.
How can they go to Heaven when they are 35 and they are awful bad? Put them in Hell.
We are mean. Human beings are mean.
There was so much opposition to that idea, it's not even funny.
And it is not coincidental that Latifah hands... Carole... Caroline hands Otis a button, this button here.
Today, was it? Did she give it to you today? ...yesterday? Yesterday. And he comes to me 5 minutes before, before the KHUTBAH to give me this button
which says
Everything up to the age of 40 is just rehearsal.
Now, I thought she made the button, but she didn't.
Where did you get it?
Carole: I don’t know. I was in a shop but I don’t know what shop I was in.
The messenger: Oh... Oh...but you picked it up in a shop. You were shopping and you saw that.
Carole: Yeah, and I saw it and I said Alhamdullilah.
The messenger: OK. So, it's not coincidence, you know. God spreads His information in many different ways,
ways and means.
Another... other secrets of the Quran that we've been enjoying in the last 10 years... Oh, the ZAKAT. Now, this is new.
And I'm gonna tell you about it now and you will have to do it, as of now, immediately. The ZAKAT... The ZAKAT is being done wrong all over the Muslim world.
Now, here is the true ZAKAT from the Quran
in SURA 6 verse 141. Yes, it is 6:141.
You remember... You're gonna remember this verse because it says when you harvest the crop, give the ZAKAT on the day of harvest.
You remember that?
On the day of harvest.
OK. Well, we are not farmers. We don't harvest wheat and barley or anything.
But we harvest paychecks every two weeks or so. That's our harvest.
The day you receive your harvest, the day you receive your paycheck, you take out 2.5% and you give it to people that you know who are in need.
It makes so much sense... I mean, how come we didn’t think of this, you know, all the time? That makes so much sense and it is from the Quran and it will correct the method of ZAKAT
that is dominant in the Muslim world.
Because the people that we know who need help, they need it now. They are hungry now.
They can't wait for a year, like they told us in the past.
You get 10 dollars, you take out 25 cents. 2.5%. Is it 25 cent? Yeah.
Now, if it is impractical to give 25 cents to somebody you know, you can keep it
and accumulate it for a couple of weeks or a month, until it is a reasonable amount. Then you give it
that month. Don't go beyond a month.
You give it to somebody you know personally, according to the system of the Quran,
your parents first, your relatives next, the orphans and the people who need it, in that order.
Any money, any net income that you get, you take 2.5% because God says. Chances are this 2.5% that you have in your check are illegitimate, illicit.
Get rid of it.
It is called purifying your money.
You spend most of your time sleeping on the job or something.
Yet, you get the check, you know. So, God says this is way you purify your income.
Take it out immidietly.
Also, who's gonna keep track of one year?
So, God has His ways. This is one of the secrets of the Quran. We reap these benefits.
Among the secrets of Quran that we've enjoyed in the last 10 years
are the correct method of the SALAT prayer.
I wanna... We're running out of time. So, TUBU ILLA ALLAH, repent.
ALHAMDULLILAH WA ASHHADU AN LA ILLAHA WAHDAHU LA SHARIKA LAH
We devote our worship and our devotion to God Alone. No human beings.
There's a SURA in Quran that says when God's victory comes and support and you see the people entering God's religion, God's true religion
in throngs, in great numbers.
And this is what is happening now.
This SURA is 19 words, consists of 19 words and the first verse is 19 letters.
This is our SURA. And this is... and so far, this bombshell... the reaction has been positive.
People have been calling me from everywhere in the world saying I'm calling to say I believe.
And when that difficult day came and I was a coward and I was saying this thing here may cause my own children to disown me. They may say you're a crazy man. Get out of here.
And, as I will tell you in detail. I cried. I fell prostrate. I was fired. I was fired.
And I cried. I fell prostrate and I begged. And when, in my heart, I became solid and I said
I will do it a any cost. Even if I lose my own children, my own friends, I will do it.
Then, I was restored, as I will give the details. I give you. But the reason I'm mentioning this SURA, the victory, is that... I went
I mean, there's unanimous, unanimous positive reaction to it from everybody... people here who read it and I went... I was very careful talking to Beth
as we were... 3 o'clock in the morning and I told her guess what, Beth?
I have to this and this and this and I was very careful diplomatic.
And then she's casually drinking her tea and she says I knew that all along, dad. I support all the way.
أعوذ بِٱللَّهِ مِنَ ٱلشَّيْطَـٰنِ ٱلرَّجِيمِ
بِسْمِ اللهِ الرَّحْمٰنِ الرَّحِيْمِ
(36:1) يسٓ
(36:2) وَٱلْقُرْءَانِ ٱلْحَكِيمِ
(36:3) إِنَّكَ لَمِنَ ٱلْمُرْسَلِينَ
(36:4) عَلَىٰ صِرَٰطٍ مُّسْتَقِيمٍ
(36:5) تَنزِيلَ ٱلْعَزِيزِ ٱلرَّحِيمِ
(36:6) لِتُنذِرَ قَوْمًا مَّآ أُنذِرَ ءَابَآؤُهُمْ فَهُمْ غَـٰفِلُونَ
(36:7) لَقَدْ حَقَّ ٱلْقَوْلُ عَلَىٰٓ أَكْثَرِهِمْ فَهُمْ لَا يُؤْمِنُونَ
(36:8) إِنَّا جَعَلْنَا فِىٓ أَعْنَـٰقِهِمْ أَغْلَـٰلًا فَهِىَ إِلَى ٱلْأَذْقَانِ فَهُم مُّقْمَحُونَ
وَجَعَلْنَا مِنۢ بَيْنِ أَيْدِيهِمْ سَدًّا وَمِنْ خَلْفِهِمْ سَدًّا فَأَغْشَيْنَـٰهُمْ فَهُمْ (36:9) لَا يُبْصِرُونَ
(36:10) وَسَوَآءٌ عَلَيْهِمْ ءَأَنذَرْتَهُمْ أَمْ لَمْ تُنذِرْهُمْ لَا يُؤْمِنُونَ
إِنَّمَا تُنذِرُ مَنِ ٱتَّبَعَ ٱلذِّكْرَ وَخَشِىَ ٱلرَّحْمَـٰنَ بِٱلْغَيْبِ ۖ فَبَشِّرْهُ (36:11) بِمَغْفِرَةٍ وَأَجْرٍ كَرِيمٍ
إِنَّا نَحْنُ نُحْىِ ٱلْمَوْتَىٰ وَنَكْتُبُ مَا قَدَّمُوا۟ وَءَاثَـٰرَهُمْ ۚ وَكُلَّ شَىْءٍ (36:12) أَحْصَيْنَـٰهُ فِىٓ إِمَامٍ مُّبِينٍ
But that night, in April, I opened Quran as usual and read the place where usually... the top right. And it said you're going to hell.
So, I closed it again and said this is Satan telling me, trying to fighting me with giving me bad time. So, I said
أعوذ بِٱللَّهِ مِنَ ٱلشَّيْطَـٰنِ ٱلرَّجِيمِ
And please God protect me from Satan. I seek refuge in You. And I said it in many different ways
and then I opened it again at random as usual and it said you're fired. You will not do the job. You're a chicken. You're not suitable. And you are going to hell.
So, I sought refuge in God again from Satan, from the devil in stronger terms for a longer time. I made SUJUD
Then, I opened the Quran again at random. It said you're fired. You're going to hell. You're doomed. You're not gonna do it. We'll find somebody else to do the job.
So, I closed it again. It is now defying statistics or coincidence.
So, I turned to God very hard and I said please, God, let me know if this is coincidence or why is it giving me these bad ideas.
So, I opened and I kept doing this and repeatedly every time, I opened. It said you're fired. You're no good. You're going to hell. You're doomed.
And it was getting worse. Until I reached the conviction, a real conviction in my heart, that I'm doomed. I'm going to hell.
Then, I started to cry. And I started to repent. And I opened it and as if the Quran had nothing in it except you're fired. You're going to hell.
You're not gonna do the work. We'll substitute somebody in your place. So, I said this Quran is rigged. Maybe, because I'm using it a lot.
So, I got this one which was brand new. And I opened it. It said you're fired. You're going to hell. You cannot do the job. You're a chicken. We'll substitute somebody in your place.
So, I closed it again and I opened another place. The Quran had nothing in it except... I got the English Quran and I opened it.
I looked in a neutral spot and it.
You're fired. You'll not do the job. You're going to Hell.
So, it is no longer coincidence. I got this big book, this big Quran, here.
And I opened it this way. I mean, I did all kinds of crazy things to let the Quran open at random and go like this.
And then I opened the Quran and looked in it. And it say you're going to hell. You're doomed. You cannot do the job. You're fired.
So, with this, I got... Oh, I got a letter opener and I stacked the Qurans
like this and I point. I closed my eyes and pointed the letter opener
and inserted it in one of these pages and opened it
and it tell me the same thing. There was nothing in the Quran that morning except you're fired. You cannot do the job. Get out of here. You're doomed. I don't need you anymore. I substitute somebody else in your place.
So, I cried and I made SUJUD. And I repented. I sought refuge from Satan and it kept giving me the same message.
So, I became convinced that God is speaking to me through the Quran and I became convinced that I'm no good,
that I'm fired, that I'm going to hell. And I cried as hard as I never did in my life.
I really became convinced that I'm finished and I'm doomed and there is no salvation inside.
I... my SUJUD became longer, my crying was harder. There was nobody in the mosque.
And then one time, I opened the Quran and it said We forgive you. Oh, I reached the conviction with all this crying that...
now, the message was very clear that I am not coming out with an announcement that I am God's messenger.
I have known it since 1980 and I ignored messages that say... there are verses in Quran that say say O, people I'm God's messenger to all of you.
And I ignored those. They were very loud and very clear and I ignored them. Obviously, the timing was not right, then. I mean, now in retrospect
I was supposed to have ignored those messages. They got loud and repeated and louder and clearer and I kept ignoring them until this happened. So, there is something that led to this.
I mean, I opened the Quran says say O, people I'm God's messenger for all of you.
And I became convinced that this is no longer the case. Then, with these repetitions, I reached the decision... in my repentance,
I said please God accept my repentance. Take me back even if I lose my own children, my friends, if I lose everybody, I will, I will do anything. I will go out and I will make the announcement.
And I really had that conviction cause I said chances are my children will tell me get out of here. You're a crazy man. What are you talking about?
So, it became my neck. And there are verses in Quran where it says the person disowns his own parents, his own children. The children disown their parents and so on. It became a reality for me.
And here I am doomed, going to hell. And all things are hinging on courage. God doesn’t want a coward to work for Him.
It became very obvious.
So, when I really reached the conviction that I will do it at any expense, I got this message that said you're forgiven. We'll accept your repentance.
And my crying of sadness became crying of joy.
And I still didn’t believe that remark. Maybe, it's a fluke.
So, I did the same thing and there was nothing in the Quran except We accept your repentance. You're forgiven. Go now and do the job. God is Forgiver, Merciful.
And I did it in the same way. I mean, this defied all statistic and all coincidence.
The background to this...
This is why I'm not... people who around me know that I'm not making any bones about it. I'm not being humble about it and I could not take any chances.
And I believe if it happens again, I will be really fired and be sent to Hell. And I'm not gonna do it. So, this is why I have been bold.
And it really has nothing to do with humbleness or modesty. If we understand a few basic things in the Quran. One thing is that a messenger is no big deal.
That it is a big deal only if we idolize the messengers. We get the picture in our mind...
...and this is the typical response with all the believers.
The people who were averse from the beginning, they just continued to be averse or maybe a little bit worse.
Except their harsh attacks had a little bit of reverence in, as if in the background, it said what if he is?
I get this telephone calls on the machine and in the past, they used to call me bad names and all that but
now they say... they read Quran. And they read the verses that says fear God.
And then they add come back to Islam. This kind of thing. But you can sense the kind of respect they have at the back of their mind.
This is the difference that happened with the opponents.
And this is because of their reverence for RASOOL ALLAH. This word, they made it so big and put it next to God.
And this is why it's a big deal for them.
But if we understand the Quran, we'll find out that it is not a big deal
because the Quran teaches us that a messenger is not necessarily better
than anyone in the world, in his generation, or anyone around him.
We have this lesson in SURA 18, where Moses, one of the big messengers of God,
met someone who's described as one of God's servants one of our servants. God says.
And this one of God's servants began teaching Moses a few lessons and Moses turned out to be a lousy student.
So, this is teaching us that the messenger, the biggest ones, are not any better than anyone around them. I mean, not necessarily better than people around them.
The Quran teaches that say I'm a human being like you. And this is about the prophet Muhammad, for example.
The Quran teaches that the criterion for closeness to God is righteousness, not being a messenger or not being the most knowledgeable or the richest or the tallest
or anything else. Righteousness. Nothing else. So, and anyone can be more righteous than the messenger or anybody else.
There is also a verse in SURA 39 that says that being a messenger of God does not even guarantee Heaven. It is no guarantee.
It says. I'm quoting the Quran, now. It says that's what We revealed to you and to those before you that if you ever fall in idol worship, in idolatry, all your work will be nullified and you'll be a loser.
So, if people understand this, they won't make a big deal out of being a messenger of God. I called Atef and I told him about this.
and he... logically, he started to discuss the wisdom of making an announcement like this and why is it necessary.
And I found myself him and I talking as if I sat down and decided to make an announcement. Then, it dawned on me it's not really my decision. It was not my decision at all.
Obviously, God wants this announcement to be made for reasons that only God knows.
And we can speculate on.
The first verse in SURA 67 says God created death and life to test us, to test the people.
Cause before that there was no death. Before the human race came here, there was no death. This is why God says He created death.
mentioned death before life.
The whole purpose is a test. And it turns out and we know now that the road to God is full of traps on the side for people to fall off. They drop out.
And when you hear somebody say I'm a messenger of God. Some people drop out. And it's part of the sifting process. There are so many traps along the road.
And the matter is decided, really, from the very beginning. I mean, a person who has doubts, who is not a sincere believer will fall off at one of these traps along the road.
The firm believer will keep going, no matter what happens. Because what we're saying is worship God Alone. We are saying destroy all idols.
And we are fanatically against building idols.
This reminds me of... I don't know if it's a good joke. I mean, there's nothing bad about the language but...
The Muhammadans insist on putting Muhammad's name next to God and say
لا إله إلا الله محمد رسول الله
In the AZAN they say لا إله إلا الله محمد رسول الله
So, I'm tempted to ask them how do you like if we follow your method and, you know, we say
لا إله إلا الله
That's it. There is no god except the One God.
لا إله إلا الله This is like the Quran says.
Verse 18 of SURA 3, God says شَهِدَ ٱللَّهُ God bears witness
أَنَّهُۥ لَآ إِلَـٰهَ إِلَّا هُوَ
that there is no god except Him.
In other words, God's SHAHADA is لا إله إلا الله
And then the verse goes on and says وَٱلْمَلَـٰٓئِكَةُ also the Angels
وَأُو۟لُوا۟ ٱلْعِلْمِ and those who posses knowledge.
This is their shahada. لا إله إلا الله So, it's very clear in the Quran that the SHAHADA is
لا إله إلا الله They insist because of idolatry to add
the Muhammad's name which violates a good number of commandments in the Quran.
When you put Muhammad's name next to God in the so-called SHAHADA, their SHAHADA,
they are violating a good number of commandments. So, the temptation is, I wanna
tell them how do you like if we say لا إله إلا الله رشاد رسول الله if we follow your method.
Now that they picked up this opposition to me... the Muhammadans... and to the point that I'm under death sentence in a good number of countries, now,
Saudi Arabia is one of them. Iran is another one. So, now that they hate me so much, how would they like to say
لا إله إلا الله رشاد رسول الله
if I give them enough proof and so on.
Maybe, this will induce them to just say لا إله إلا الله
So, we are saying لا إله إلا الله
We are, very strongly, starchly against building any idol. And
I don’t know how to convince them that I don’t want any glory or money or fame.
And for 8 years, I was really... I was a coward.
I mean, what did this announcement bring to me? Except, I thought trouble.
but it did not, actually. Their action has been positive so far.
But I would rather go and worship God Alone by myself somewhere very quietly and just eke out and living out of this world and go into the eternal life.
This is what I would rather do, personally.
This is what I wanted to do for 8 years. This is why I was fired in that night.
So, I'm sure I forgot quite a few points that I wanted to tell you about.
The background to this is that I have known since 1980
that I'm God's messenger in the sense that... not in a general sense... in the sense that Abraham was the original messenger of Islam.
He brought all the practices.
The NAMAZ, the fasting, the ZAKAT Charity, pilgrimage
and of course the first commandment لا إله إلا الله
and Muhammad brought the Quran. And that I am the third of a triangle that I brought the proof...
the proof of authenticity of the religion.
The first publication... we just found out this yesterday... The first time the miracle of Quran was published
was in January 1973.
1973, I was 38 years old and I didn’t know anything except that I found this mathematical miracle in the Quran.
And the 7th... the January 73 publication in the most popular magazine in the middle east: آخر الساعة
had to do with the proportion of the initials. Qaf, for example, the letter Q in chapter 50.
That chapter had the highest proportion of the letter Q.
SURA Saad had the highest proportion of the letter Saad. SURA NuN had the highest proportion of SURA NuN. Alef Lam Meemm and so on.
Every SURA had the highest proportion of its initials except SURA Ya Seen had the least... the exact opposite. And that was the whole article.
And it didn’t have the computer printouts of the whole Quran which I had written in the computer.
And then in 1973, in November
which is exactly my 38th birthday was the first report on the number 19. That was back in 73.
And... but I didn’t know that I am God's messenger in that sense until 1980.
1980 was correspondent to the year 1400, the Islamic year. And
it seems like a new era began at that time, 1400. If you look here
in SURA 47.... SURA 47, verse 38. 38 was very prominent. We were looking at this magazine yesterday
We became curious... We were looking at it on the other page.
They had reports in the magazine 38 years ago. They had a big number 38.
47, the last verse which is 38.
I wrote in bold letters that if you turn away, God will substitute other people in your place
and they will not be like you. This is one of the verses, by the way, about substituting somebody in your place.
But then I wrote this in bold... in big letters and I put a footnote saying here.... at the end of the footnote it says Islam is being reestablished in the English-speaking world
after being restored to its pristine purity.
So, I wrote here, back in 1980, 1400 that God had forsaken the Arabs. The Arabs meaning in the Arabian peninsula.
There's a certain geographical area where the Arabs are... that defines who the Arabs are.
And now, it's been 8 years and we didn't have... we don't have a single Arab. Of the hundred million Arabs in the world, we don't have a single Arab who could see and appreciate the miracle of Quran
even though it's very clear.
An Arab, from the Arabian peninsula, not from North Africa and not from Egypt.
Sometimes they call me and say you're an Arab, aren't you? I say No, Thank God. I'm Egyptian.
But it's quite a phenomenon that we don’t have a single Arab.
Last Friday, we had like 60 people in the mosque, not a single Arab.
We had the conference in San Francisco, couple of hundred people, not a single Arab except those who came to harass us.
So, there's.... something happened in 1980 after 7 pairs of centuries.
SURA 13... 15 excuse me. SURA 15, verse 87. God is telling Muhammad I'm giving you 7 pairs.
Among the other meanings, I'm convinced that it means 7 pairs of centuries because of what I've seen and
the fact that this verse is at the end of SURA entitled Muhammad.
So, the background is that I have known since 1980 and I have been evading the responsibility of... Actually, we'll just go, just go along and worship God and spread the message.
And what we've been doing was... God has been gracious to us in that He's been showing us what the correct Islam is.
The Muhammadans, throughout the world, the hundred million of them are doing SALAT wrong,
they mention محمد آل محمد. ابراهیم آل ابراهیم
in the SALAT. We know now for sure that this is wrong.
The Quran came out of Muhammad's mouth. It says you should never mention any other name during the SALAT
besides other than the name of God. That the SALAT must be devoted to God Alone and no one else. So, they did the SALAT wrong. They did the ZAKAT wrong.
They are doing it wrong. And now we have it corrected.
If we look in SURA 6, verse 141, it tells you when you harvest the fruits or the crops,
give the charity, the ZAKAT charity of that crop on the day of harvest.
Now, the ZAKAT as being practiced now in the Muhammadan world is once a year
on your savings, above a certain amount.
But the Quran says give the ZAKAT on the day of harvest.
Now, since we are not farmers, we do not harvest fruits or crops, or anything like that. We harvest paychecks.
So, when we get the paycheck, we're supposed to take out
what came to us from IBRAHIM in very clear words ربع العشر a quarter of ten. One quarter of one ten. This comes to 2.5 percent.
So, you take 2.5% of your net income when you get it, the day you get it.
So, I would... I would go...
I would say it makes sense that we wait like a month to know what our month seems, we get our paychecks, our monthly income. It's a very common thing.
And you, at the end of the month, figure out how much was your net income, 2.5 percent and you give it to people you personally know are in need.
You know them, personally and you know that they need the assistance.
And we are given specific order in the Quran as to who we give the money to.
You give it first to your parents.
If they don’t need it, you give it to your relatives, cousins, and uncles and aunts and so on.
People you know, personally who are related to you and they need the money or the help.
After that, the orphans. You find children who lost one or both parents
for some reason, divorce or abandonment or death and you give them this money.
And the fourth category is any poor persons and the last category are traveling aliens
people who sneak into this country from Mexico. They have no jobs. They are hungry. So, you help them. We have a specific order in the Quran.
This is the correct ZAKAT. So, what we did was, we cleaned out the SALAT. We returned it to its pristine purity.
We corrected the ZAKAT. We corrected the fasting. Even the fasting was wrong.
What SURA?
What was wrong with it? Well, they sleep all day and stay up all night and use fasting as an excuse to be nasty and...
You know that. They call names and say I'm fasting. So, excuse me, I'm fasting.
And the timing of the moon is always wrong.
I think they're fasting today, still in Egypt. And even though, tonight you can see the moon.
I'd love to go out, but the computer tells you what time the moon is born,
what time it rises, what time it sets.
and whether the clouds or not, whether inside or not, whether you are sighted or blind, you can know exactly
what the moon is doing.
But they follow the Hadith that says you fast when you see it,
and you break your fast when you don't see it.
and if you cannot see it, you complete the month of Ramadan, 30 days. So,
we fasted 29 days this month.
Audience: Is it 29 days all the time?
The messenger: No, sometimes 29, sometimes 30.
The Hajj was wrong and we already wrote in the Muslim Perspective to correct... Hajj is wrong by going to Medina.
It turns out that, as it is now done, going to Medina is the most important part of Hajj even though it is not part of Hajj at all in the Quran.
Going to Medina is flagrant idol worship. They go to the prophet's tomb or to Fatimah's tomb and they pray and implore.
Nothing. I'm quoting the Quran because on the Day of Judgement say we were worshipping nothing.
So, this is what we've been doing and I was happy that way. So, we were just spreading the message. It has gone all over the world, literally.
This... this translation and the small book, the brown book, Quran, Hadith and Islam
and the message of returning Islam to its pristine purity as far as all the practices are concerned.
These places, I never heard of, little islands in the Indian ocean.
There's an island called l'union? Union Island in English? But it's a French... l'union.
Ihsan lived in Mauritius. That's another country I never heard of, Mauritius. And we have people there in Mauritius.
l'union? l'union? Close?
Are they close to Mauritius? It must be.
I went to New Zealand, Australia. I went everywhere and I was happy that way. The message is being spread all over the world.
Exactly what needs to be done.
So, why the announcement? That was my justification.
And that's why each one of you asked me why the announcement? Why is it necessary?
So, my opinion was the same as yours. But then, I was...
Pardon?
Right. OK. What do they have?
Obviously, God has a reason. The Quran says you don't ask God why. We ask.
God is not to be asked about anything He does but we are to be asked about anything we do.
(21:23) لَا يُسْـَٔلُ عَمَّا يَفْعَلُ وَهُمْ يُسْـَٔلُونَ
So, obviously God has a purpose and very good reasons. Now, the Quran says that Muhammad is not the last messenger.
And this could be one the very important reasons.
So, if Muhammad is not the last messenger... The statement in the Quran in 33:40 says
مَّا كَانَ مُحَمَّدٌ أَبَآ أَحَدٍ مِّن رِّجَالِكُمْ Muhammad was not the father of any of your men
وَلَـٰكِن رَّسُولَ ٱللَّه a messenger of God وَخَاتَمَ ٱلنَّبِيِّـۧنَ and the final prophet
This expression of رَّسُولَ ٱللَّه. وَلَـٰكِن رَّسُولَ ٱللَّه
is not necessary at all for the meaning. If the prophet include the messenger or vice versa.
You can have a perfect sentence saying
مَّا كَانَ مُحَمَّدٌ أَبَآ أَحَدٍ مِّن رِّجَالِكُمْ وَلَـٰكِن خَاتَمَ ٱلنَّبِيِّـۧنَ
Muhammad was not the father of any of your men but he was the final prophet.
But of course every letter in the Quran is delivered as we know now, very well. It says
وَلَـٰكِن رَّسُولَ ٱللَّه a messenger of God وَخَاتَمَ ٱلنَّبِيِّـۧنَ and the final prophet
So, there is a verse 35 in SURA 7 says O, children of Adam when messengers come to you
narrating My revelations to you, those of you who believe and lead a righteous life
are the successful ones.
Obviously, this is a verse for the people after Muhammad because it's in the Quran.
And like Dr. Mansour said for as long as there are children of Adam on Earth, this verse is valid. Because it says O, children of Adam
In Arabic
يَـٰبَنِىٓ ءَادَمَ إِمَّا يَأْتِيَنَّكُمْ رُسُلٌ مِّنكُمْ يَقُصُّونَ عَلَيْكُمْ ءَايَـٰتِى ۙ (7:35) فَمَنِ ٱتَّقَىٰ وَأَصْلَحَ فَلَا خَوْفٌ عَلَيْهِمْ وَلَا هُمْ يَحْزَنُونَ
35, SURA 7.
So, I mean, what is this verse directed to? Not the people before Muhammad because they've never seen the Quran.
For the people who read the Quran.
The Quran gives us all sorts of example of the human tendency or aversion to the idea of having a messenger of God.
It seems to be a test of ego, a test of ego, you know. This guy is gonna sit here and say I'm messenger of God. So, he's gonna steal the show. And
he's gonna get all the attention.
And it may be one of the tests, you know, for dropping out. This is something I don't wanna contribute to that. But it's not up to me.
So, the Quran illustrates this by using Joseph. Joseph... this is verse... I believe it's verse 34 in SURA 40.
SURA 40, it says Joseph had come to you with clear revelations, but you doubted his message. Then, when he died you said he was the last messenger.
Now, look who God picks out. Joseph. Who came after Joseph? The big ones. What are the big ones? David, Solomon, Jesus, Moses, Muhammad.
All these came after Joseph even though the people said he's the last messenger. Nobody else will come after that.
So, they have been saying the same thing about Muhammad
that Muhammad is the last messenger.
The world population today is a thousand times what it was at the time of Muhammad. And you've seen how much advancement the human being achieved.
This is an enlightened generation of humans who are very advanced,
computers, and sciences, and technology and video tapes.
And it just makes sense that God wants to send a messenger to this generation.
And I can't make any bones about it. I can't.
I'm chickened the other way around now.
I was a chicken in being afraid to announce and now I'm a chicken not to... I'm a chicken to hold back.
Cause I'm afraid if I'm fired again, there will be no restoration.
So, this verse about Joseph tells us that it's a human tendency.
And now the question to turn the table around... the question is why are they averse to this idea?
So, if Muhammad was not the last messenger and somebody is gonna come after Muhammad, messengers after Muhammad. What do they look like?
What are their qualifications? What will they say?
So, if someone comes along and says worship God Alone.
Uphold the word of God Alone, not the words of men. Clean out all the practices of worship. Destroy all idols. Remove all innovations.
What's wrong with that?
I mean, it makes sense that God's messenger will do that, will say that.
Why will I oppose or object to someone who says that?
We'll get along just fine. With any one of us.
This is really the same message from Adam until now. It's one and the same message.
So, I along with you would ask that question, you know. And I put it in the Perspective. They should tell us why shouldn't I be a messenger of God?
I've given them enough proof. I've had lots of, there's a lot of evidence in that.
And it is mathematical. It is physical, tangible.
So, I want them to come up with evidence opposing that that I should not be.
There's one thing that came out.
The first thing that came out I'm thinking of some Muslim organization in Oklahoma
and they issued the new magazine. The first issue. I think it was just for that and there was an article in it. said that my name is not Rashad Khalifa.
my name is not Rashad Khalifa. I mean, I've heard everything now.
بِسْمِ اللهِ الرَّحْمٰنِ الرَّحِيْمِ
(36:1) يسٓ
(36:2) وَٱلْقُرْءَانِ ٱلْحَكِيمِ
(36:3) إِنَّكَ لَمِنَ ٱلْمُرْسَلِينَ
(36:4) عَلَىٰ صِرَٰطٍ مُّسْتَقِيمٍ
(36:5) تَنزِيلَ ٱلْعَزِيزِ ٱلرَّحِيمِ
(36:6) لِتُنذِرَ قَوْمًا مَّآ أُنذِرَ ءَابَآؤُهُمْ فَهُمْ غَـٰفِلُونَ
(36:7) لَقَدْ حَقَّ ٱلْقَوْلُ عَلَىٰٓ أَكْثَرِهِمْ فَهُمْ لَا يُؤْمِنُونَ
(36:8) إِنَّا جَعَلْنَا فِىٓ أَعْنَـٰقِهِمْ أَغْلَـٰلًا فَهِىَ إِلَى ٱلْأَذْقَانِ فَهُم مُّقْمَحُونَ
وَجَعَلْنَا مِنۢ بَيْنِ أَيْدِيهِمْ سَدًّا وَمِنْ خَلْفِهِمْ سَدًّا فَأَغْشَيْنَـٰهُمْ فَهُمْ (36:9) لَا يُبْصِرُونَ
(36:10) وَسَوَآءٌ عَلَيْهِمْ ءَأَنذَرْتَهُمْ أَمْ لَمْ تُنذِرْهُمْ لَا يُؤْمِنُونَ
إِنَّمَا تُنذِرُ مَنِ ٱتَّبَعَ ٱلذِّكْرَ وَخَشِىَ ٱلرَّحْمَـٰنَ بِٱلْغَيْبِ ۖ فَبَشِّرْهُ (36:11) بِمَغْفِرَةٍ وَأَجْرٍ كَرِيمٍ
إِنَّا نَحْنُ نُحْىِ ٱلْمَوْتَىٰ وَنَكْتُبُ مَا قَدَّمُوا۟ وَءَاثَـٰرَهُمْ ۚ وَكُلَّ شَىْءٍ (36:12) أَحْصَيْنَـٰهُ فِىٓ إِمَامٍ مُّبِينٍ
(36:24) إِنِّىٓ إِذًۭا لَّفِى ضَلَـٰلٍۢ مُّبِينٍ
So, they did the SALAT wrong. They did the ZAKAT wrong. They are doing it wrong.
And now we have it corrected.
If we look in SURA 6, verse 141, it tells you when you harvest the fruits or the crops, give the charity, the ZAKAT charity of that crop on the day of harvest.
Now, the ZAKAT as being practiced now in the Muhammadan world is once a year on your savings, above a certain amount.
But the Quran says give the ZAKAT on the day of harvest.
Now, since we are not farmers, we do not harvest fruits or crops, or anything like that. We harvest paychecks.
So, when we get the paycheck, we're supposed to take out
what came to us from IBRAHIM in very clear words ربع العشر a quarter of ten. One quarter of one ten. This comes to 2.5 percent.
So, you take 2.5% of your net income when you get it, the day you get it. So, I would... I would go...
I would say it makes sense that we wait like a month to know what our month seems, we get our paychecks, our monthly income. It's a very common thing.
And you, at the end of the month, figure out how much was your net income, 2.5 percent and you give it to people you personally know are in need.
You know them, personally, and you know that they need the assistance. And we are given specific order in the Quran as to who we give the money to.
You give it first to your parents. If they don’t need it, you give it to relatives, cousins, and uncles and aunts and so on. People you know, personally
who are related to you and they need the money or the help. After that, the orphans. You find children who lost one or both parents
for some reason, divorce or abandonment or death and you give them this money. And the fourth category is any poor persons and the last category are traveling aliens
people who sneak into this country from Mexico. They have no jobs. They are hungry. So, you help them.
We have a specific order in the Quran. This is the correct ZAKAT.
So, what we did was, we cleaned out the SALAT. We returned it to its pristine purity.
We corrected the ZAKAT. We corrected the fasting. Even the fasting was wrong.
What SURA?
What was wrong with it? Well, they sleep all day and stay up all night and use fasting as an excuse to be nasty and...
You know that. They call names and then say I am fasting. So, excuse me, I'm fasting.
And the timing of the moon is always wrong.
I think they're fasting today, still in Egypt. And even though, tonight you can see the moon.
I'd love to go out, but
the computer tells you what time the moon is born, what time it rises, what time it sets
and whether the clouds or not, whether inside or not, whether you are sighted or blind, you can know exactly what the moon is doing.
But they follow the Hadith that says you fast when you see it, and you break your fast when you don't see it.
and if you cannot see it, you complete the month of Ramadan, 30 days. So, we fasted 29 days this month.
Audience: Is it 29 days all the time?
The messenger: No, sometimes 29, sometimes 30.
The Hajj was wrong and we already wrote in the Muslim Perspective to correct... Hajj is wrong by going to Medina.
It turns out that, as it is now done, going to Medina is the most important part of Hajj even though it is not part of Hajj at all in the Quran.
Going to Medina is flagrant idol worship. They go to the prophet's tomb or to Fatimah's tomb and they pray and implore.
Nothing. I'm quoting the Quran because on the Day of Judgement say we were worshipping nothing.
So, this is what we've been doing and I was happy that way. So, we were just spreading the message. It has gone all over the world, literally.
This... this translation and the small book, the brown book, Quran, Hadith and Islam and the message of returning Islam to its pristine purity as far as all the practices are concerned.
These places, I never heard of...